Friends, you can get insurance for your bike from the Fpay application
and I will
tell you the complete method of getting it. So look,
I am on this page right now, I will show you how to get to this page.
First of all, open your PhonePe.
You will see a page like this.
In this page, you have to
scroll down a little and you will
see an insurance tab. If you can't
see it, then you will see the
insurance button below. There are five buttons among
them, the insurance button is there.
Click on it. Here you will see "
Insure Your Vehicle" right in front. Now,
I had entered some of my details,
so its details are visible at the top.
But if you want to get it for any other bike,
you can get it from here. A page will appear in front of you, whether it
is a bike or a car, you can decide from there. For example, if it
is a bike, I will go to bike
and it will appear here. Then this
page will open in front of you. You have to enter
your vehicle number, as we
entered it. After entering this number, you have to
submit. As soon as you submit, it will appear in front of you.
Which plan are you taking,
what is its duration? Personal
accident cover has to be added at the bottom.  Whether you do not have to
enter it and below you will see different codes from different
insurance companies,
you can choose which one you want to take, so
if you want to take something other than comprehensive, or
third party, then you
click here, if you want to take
comprehensive, take comprehensive, then
you can choose the plan from here, only
two plans are visible here at present,
you have to select the duration, brother, are you
taking it for one year, two years,
three years, you
can select how much you are taking as per your wish,
so here you will see, at the bottom you will
find another button of personal accident cover, if
you click on it, you will come to know that
brother, you get a cover of Rs 15 lakh,
if there is a death or any
type of hospitalization, then you can turn it on,
one thing will happen that on turning it on,
your price of insurance
increases a little, so you have to see,
I am not taking it here at the moment, below
you can decide the company  Decide from whom you
want to buy brother, there are many different companies,
you must have seen what their plans are,
so you can check that here or if
you want to buy the cheapest one then you
can choose that from here also,
they have not given any option to sort which
I found strange thing, now you have to see one more thing
that how much IDV are you getting here,
how much value of your vehicle are you getting, that
is different in different plans, you see this one is taking ₹ 37 and is
also giving 225000 ID, if you
see the one below then it is giving 9500, giving ₹ 1 for the
value of the vehicle and taking ₹ 1 from me, so
I am choosing IIC ID here,
I bought this here, so
see they gave me the details of my bike,
which bike it is, you will get to know here
because you had entered the number, on the top side
you see the applied NCB, there is nothing
left of the previous NCB, so it
is visible here at 0  The engine number will be
given to you here. If you want, you
can see more details as well. Below you
will see personal details as to in whose name the vehicle
is. Now you have to see this plan. Now you must be thinking that it was
showing 737 there, but here it has become
870, so how so you
can see its amount breakup. Click on it from here. The
basic third party liability was ₹ 7714, the
own damage premium was ₹
and after applying GST it became ₹ 1.33, 870 total
amount. Now you have to buy the plan.
After doing this, you just have to make the payment
as we always do
and enter your UPI PIN.
After entering the UPI PIN, you will submit.
You can see that the payment has been
successful, then the next page comes.
You have to do KYC. If it is mandatory, then
you can do KYC. You will have to
submit some details. Let's
see what you have to do. So you have to enter the PAN number here.
After entering the PIN, you have to enter your date of birth,
which you have to select from here.
After entering the details, if you want to
enter your email ID, you can do so,
otherwise it is optional, it will be fine if you don't enter it, you just have to
submit it, you can see
that brother, you have received your policy here, it is
showing you here, it is a
comprehensive cover from 8th June till today's date,
for one year of next year, the
IDV is visible here,
you will get the vehicle information from here, you will get the owner
driver from here, you will get the policy
document, if you want to download then
you can also do the email option from here, if you have
given your email then you can find it there too, I will
download it here, so now see it is
downloading and then we will open it, then
you can see that my
insurance has come here and you
can see all these details here, so it is
that simple to buy insurance through Phone Pay,
if you still have any questions then you
can ask in the comment section, do let
me know how you liked the video, thank you